<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
    <name>RimWorld Survival Frontier</name>
    <author>Lele</author>
    <packageId>lele.rimworldsurvivalfrontier</packageId>
    <description>## 🌨️ **Designed for Extreme Climates**
Complete survival toolkit for extreme biomes. Materials, food production, shelter - everything needed to thrive in hostile frontiers.

## 🎯 **Vanilla Friendly** :
Perfect integration with the base game. Balanced for equilibrium gameplay without disrupting the RimWorld experience.

RECENT UPDATES: 1.0.0.8 
🆕 BONUS UPDATE: 
- Chemfuel Stove now available!
- Recipe Balance: Vent recipe adjustments now you can use different material for building it. 

🗺️ NEXT UPDATE: Dried Food System
- ETA: 5-7 days        
        
## 🌱 **Ecological Production**
Create bio-plastic at the biofuel refinery from common plant resources: agave, berries, corn, potatoes, and rice.
Even greenhouse-grown crops work! No more dependence on traders for advanced materials!

## 🔧 **Six Specialized Materials**
**Plastic Basic** :
Entry-level material for basic furniture, structures, and recreation. Cheap and fast to produce. ( Biofuel refinery )

**Plastic Industrial** :
Advanced version for high-quality construction. Greater durability and beauty for your premium structures. ( Biofuel refinery )

**Plastic Bio-Steel** :
Advanced plastic bio-engineered steel created by reinforcing plant-based polymers with metallic compounds (Fabrication bench)

**Plastic Fiber** :
Synthetic textile for clothing. Sustainable alternative to cotton for dressing your colony. ( Biofuel refinery )

**Incendiary Plastic** :
Bio-plastic infused with volatile compounds. Extremely flammable material for tactical construction/floor applications. Handle with care. ( Biofuel refinery )

**Eco leather** :
Synthetic leather from plant polymers. Sustainable alternative to animal leather for high-quality clothing. ( tailor bench )

## ⚡ **Recipe for Biofuel Refinery**
- Recycle all plastics into Chemfuel! Transform waste into energy for your generators.
- Convert hay to Chemfuel
- " Recycle " corpses of humans or animals into Chemfuel! Sustainable energy solutions, saving the world is a duty.
        
## **Traders** :
Now traders bring raw resources: Plastic Basic, Plastic Industrial, Plastic Bio-Steel, Plastic Fiber, Incendiary Plastic, Eco leather and Wood Planks

## **Indoor crops** :
*Crop Basin*:
- No power required.
- Crop types: Corn, Cotton, Dandelion, Daylily, Devilstrand, Haygrass, Hops, Healroot, Potato, Psychoid, Rice, Rose, Smokeleaf, Strawberry, Tinctoria
- 120% efficiency
- Crop Basin 1x4 like Hydroponic basin
- Tiny Crop Basin 1x1
- Compact Crop Basin 1x3

*Tree Basin*:
- No power required.
- Crop types: Oak Tree, Cocoa Tree, Poplar Tree
- 80% efficiency
- Tiny 1x1

Add sun lamps
- All lamps have light range indicators
- Wall sun lamp
- Small sun lamp
- Tiny 1x1 sun lamp
- Compact 1x3 sun lamp

## **Quality of life ( QoL ) ** :
Add light range indicators to all vanilla lamps: Wall Lamp, Flood Light, Standing Lamp, Torch Lamp, and Wall Torch Lamp

🌍 **TRANSLATION REQUEST** 🌍

Want to see RimWorld Survival Frontier in your language?

Currently supported:
- English (default)
- Italian (native)

**How to help:**
1. Comment your language
2. I'll provide translation keys
3. You translate, I'll credit you!
        
Originally inspired by Plastic Revolution by Orbittwz.
https://github.com/orbittwz/PlasticRevolution .
Completely rewritten implementation with expanded survival focus.

Licensed under MIT License.
Copyright (c) 2025 Emanuele Martinelli
https://github.com/GhChancellor/RimWorldSurvivalFrontier</description>
    
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.6</li>
    </supportedVersions>
</ModMetaData>
